We are going to locate the dural sheath, the
硬膜管を探します、その
middle dural sheath. I position myself here on this coronal suture,
中硬膜管を。私はこの冠状縫合に手を置きます、
I examine each small
私はそれぞれの小さな
bevel, I check if there isn't a spicule that
縫合の傾斜面（ベベル）を注意深く確認し、歯が
protrudes or is not properly aligned.
突出していないか、または適切でないかを見ます。
you observe if the suture is harder
縫合がより硬いかどうか、
in certain areas, denser in specific locations
特定の場所でより密であるかどうかを確認します。
sometimes you encounter this
時にはそのような状態が見られます。
given this configuration, you can even experience this
そのような状態であるため、そのようなことも起こり得ます。
I verify, it's all about
私は確認します、それだけです。
it's truly important for the suture
縫合線が
to be free in its function
その機能において自由に動くことは本当に重要です。
in relation to the occlusal system
咬合システムに関して
something we assess
私たちが確認することです。
and if there is one
そしてもしそのような箇所があれば、
I specifically address it and I will
私はその箇所に直接アプローチし、
I manipulate it; this sometimes results in
それを操作します。これは時には
a very subtle
非常に小さな
release of an entire electrical field, verify that.
電場全体の解放を引き起こします。それを確認してください。
Next, I will now simply perform a rebalancing procedure.
次に、今、私は単に再均衡化の作業を行います。
I take the dural sheath, you see, and I position myself on this dural sheath,
硬膜管を取ります、ご覧の通り、そしてこの硬膜管に手を置きます、
and I know that this dural sheath, ultimately, it orients towards my cranial base.
そしてこの硬膜管は、最終的に私の頭蓋底に向かって配向していることを知っています。
So I position myself here, always considering the entirety of the body,
だから私はここに手を置きます、私は常に体全体を捉え、
I always maintain this global perspective.
常にこの全体的な視点に立ちます。
It's at the bregma level, what, bregma?
それはブレグマのレベルです、何、ブレグマ？
bregma, bregma and up to the level of the articulation,
ブレグマ、ブレグマ、そして関節のレベルまで、
the entire coronal zone.
冠状縫合全体です。
Not from bregma, very gently here. Anterior fontanelle. Up to the point
ブレグマではなく、ここでは非常にゆっくりと。前頭泉門。私が
where I
見つけるまで、
find it; she will feel it at some point, when it is
彼女はいつかそれを感じるでしょう、それが
apparent, it will
現れて、それは
feel as if...
〜のように感じるでしょう...
As if it were a melting stick of butter.
まるでバターの塊が溶けていくかのように。
As if moving from something dense towards something fluid.
まるで密なものから流動的なものへと移行するかのように。
I am seeking the fluid body of the bone.
私は骨の流動体を探しています。
As before.
先ほどのように。
When we performed the work this morning, the practice,
今朝、実習を行った際、
when you transitioned from hair to fluid at one point.
ある時点で、髪から液体へと移行した時。
Yes, exactly, that's it.
はい、そうです、まさにそれです。
But here, I am truly engaging with this sheath,
しかしここでは、私はこの鞘（シース）にしっかりと触れていますが、
but in its entirety here.
ここでは全体性の中で。
Except that I am seeking this...
ただし、私が探しているのはこの...
on the bone. Gently,
骨の上で。ゆっくりと、
I sense that it is different, that I no longer have the same
私はそれが異なり、もはや同じではないと感じます、
density. I slowly begin to enter the
密度ではないと。私はゆっくりと、
electrical field of the
の電場に入り始めます。
coronal suture. Once I have it here, I
冠状縫合の。ここでそれを捉えたら、私は
will position myself like this and I come to
このように身を置き、そして
seek this connection and I simply re-harmonize
この繋がりを探し、そして単に再調和させます
the cranial base, in another way, via the periphery.
頭蓋底を、別の方法で、周辺部から。
This is a very important work in children.
これは子供たちにとって非常に重要な施術です。
We work extensively, extensively, on the mandible,
私たちは下顎骨に、非常に、非常に多く働きかけます、
as I am doing here, in children.
私がここでしているように、子供たちに。
Babies must transition from the womb to the mouth.
赤ちゃんは、お腹から口へと移行しなければなりません。
They must have suction and lingual and maxillary activity.
彼らは吸引力と舌および上顎の活動を持つ必要があります。
This is life. I can also work on it through
それが生命です。私はそれをまた、
the anterior sheath.
前方の鞘（シース）との関連で施術することができます。
The transverse sinus, I
横静脈洞、私は
position myself here, I seek to give them either purely here
ここに身を置き、彼らに純粋にここに与えようとします
the freedom of this tissue.
この組織の自由。
So, I am truly working, you see here, it's as if I'm opening the space for
ですから、私は本当に、ご覧のように、空間を開くように働きかけています。
so that the system...
システムが...
of drainage, it's the hyper-efficient drainage.
ドレナージの、それは非常に活発なものです。
You do not always have
いつも持っているわけではありません
this awareness of this embryonic movement
この胚性運動の意識
and of the
そして
totality.
全体性。
Yes, that will be another work
はい、それは別の施術になるでしょう
that we will do when I address the entire system
私が行うことになるものです、私がシステム全体を施術するときに
vascular, where I demonstrate how
血管系で、どのように示すか
we clear in a much more
私たちは、よりはるかに
precise manner the desiccated field
正確に枯渇した領域を解放します
with
とともに
the movements
動き
fascial and the movements
顔面の動きと
of the heart.
心臓の動き。
And already, if we can properly recall the entire dynamics
そして既に、もし私たちがまだよく思い出せるなら、全てのダイナミクスを
of brain development,
脳の発達の、
all this movement with all these
この全ての動きと、これら全ての
elements, the entire ventricular movement that is present
事柄、存在している全ての脳室運動
also, to perform it in this manner, with the thumbs positioned there, to
もまた、そこにある親指でこのように行うこと、
also work each time.
毎回施術すること。
the different dural restrictions always in relation to my cranial base.
いつも私の頭蓋底に対して、様々な硬膜の制限を。
Each time, reintegrate them onto this cranial base.
毎回、それらをこの頭蓋底に再統合すること。
Naturally address the cranio-sacral axis, verify for any whiplash.
自然に頭蓋仙骨軸を施術し、むち打ち損傷がないか確認すること。
It is truly important that this cranio-sacral system
この頭蓋仙骨システムが
functions.
機能することは本当に重要です。
It is essential to have this integrated freedom in the different diaphragms.
様々な横隔膜に、この統合された自由が本当に必要です。
The diaphragm was very important.
横隔膜は非常に重要でした。
These are diaphragms at the level of the feet; they rebalance the lesser pelvis.
足部の横隔膜は、骨盤底を再均衡化します。
All issues of the lesser pelvis are related to congestive planes,
骨盤底のあらゆる問題は、鬱血性の平面に起因します。
it is sometimes due to restricted feet.
それは時に、足が自由でないことにあります。
Also, a knee technique, ensuring good
膝のテクニックも同様に、良好な
mobility, a proper re-axation of the knees.
自由度、膝の良好な再軸化を持つことです。
That it is very mobile, this is crucial.
それが十分に自由であること、それは不可欠です。
A very simple technique; there is precisely a technique of
非常にシンプルなテクニックとして、まさに
knee compression to restore mobility.
膝の圧迫により自由度を取り戻すものです。
The important viscera, the important diaphragms, and then I
重要な内臓、重要な横隔膜、そして私は
very often conclude by checking for rebalancing.
非常に頻繁に、再均衡化があるかを確認して終えます。
I work extensively by observing space.
私は空間を見ながら、多く施術します。
Alright, it's finished, it's finished, it's finished.
よし、終わりです、終わりです、終わりです。